A Guide to the Civil Appointments of the Virginia Governor's Office, 1780-1824
Library of Virginia
- Requests for remission of fines, 1783-1800.
  - Hardy County, 1798-1799. (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Harrison County, 1797, 1799. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Henrico County, 1797, 1799-1800. (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Henry County, 1787, 1799. (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Isle of Wight County, 1785, 1796. (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - James City County, 1785. (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - King and Queen County, 1793, 1796-1799. (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - King George County, 1787. (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - King William County, 1796, 1798. (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Lancaster County, 1784, 1791. (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Loudoun County, 1791, 1797, 1799. (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Louisa County, 1785-1787, 1791, 1797-1798. (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Lunenburg County, 1785. (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Marshall County, 1798. (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Mathews County, 1796-1797. (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Mecklenburg County, 1785. (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Middlesex County, 1796. (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Monongalia County, 1797, 1799. (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Montgomery County, 1798. (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Nansemond County, 1790, 1793, 1796-1799. (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - New Kent County, 1792-1800. (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Northampton County, 1785, 1787. (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Northumberland County, 1793, 1796, 1798. (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Nottoway County, 1799-1800. (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Ohio County, 1795, 1797. (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Orange County, 1787, 1791, 1795, 1798. (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Patrick County, 1798. (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Pendleton County, 1799. (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Pittsylvania County, 1795. (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Powhatan County, 1783, 1785, 1787, 1795. (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Prince Edward County, 1791, 1793, 1795-1796. (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Prince George County, 1785, 1794-1795, 1797-1799. (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Prince William County, 1792. (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Richmond County, 1797. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Rockbridge County, 1787, 1789, 1791, 1795, 1797-1798. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Rockingham County, 1785, 1787, 1791, 1799. (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Russell County, 1799. (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Southampton County, 1785, 1795, 1803. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Spotsylvania County, 1785, 1795. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Stafford County, 1795, 1797. (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Surry County, 1785, 1799. (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Sussex County, 1791, 1795, 1796. (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Warwick County, 1795. (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Westmoreland County, 1785, 1793. (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Wythe County, 1796-1798. (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - York County, 1791, 1793. (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Richmond City, 1796, 1798-1800. (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Unidentified, 1797-1799. (Box 18, Folder 15)